原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查    想念Gallifrey的Wholock
后期     累
总监     累
早餐好了  吃饭咯
Breakfast is ready, let's go.
你姐妹呢
Where's your sister?
塞拉
Sila!
快点
Come on.
这孩子
That girl...
快点啊
Come on.
我们
Let's...
克里斯托
Hey, Crystal.
塞拉昨晚没在你那儿过夜吧
Sila didn't spend the night there last night, did she?
没有吗
No?
不  她没有回家
No, she didn't come home.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂  吉姆
Hello, Jim.
塞拉不在吧
Sila isn't over there, is she?
如果她去了麻烦你告诉我一声
Well, you let me know if she comes by.
塞拉什么时候送她下车的
What time did Sila drop her off?
她说她会直接回家吗
And she said she was coming straight home?
塞拉
Sila!
911  请问有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
黄石
第三季  第六集
我们在离这里10英里的地方找到了她的车
So, we found her car about 10 miles from here.
没油了
Ran out of gas.
没有挣扎的迹象  所以我的猜测是
There's no sign of a struggle, so my guess is
她不是搭便车就是想步行
she either hitched a ride or tried to walk it.
现在还不知道是哪种情况  所以我们都纳入了考虑
There's no telling which, so for now we're assuming both.
我得派人去找她  汤姆
I need to put together a search. Tom,
但我人手不够
and I don't have the manpower.
我去联系一下
I'll make some calls.
你问过她所有的朋友了吗
Now, you checked with all her friends?
都问了
Everybody.
现在我也不知道她生还的概率有多少
At this point, I don't know what her chances are.
你心里很清楚  本
You know exactly what her chances are, Ben.
他是谁
Who is he?
就是一个交易马匹  爱撒谎的
Just a horse trading, lying...
半个罪犯
half a criminal.
里普  把牛赶到新谷仓上面去
Rip, push those cattle up to the field above the new barn.
遵命
Sir.
你们听好了  那些狗娘养的对你们说什么
Y'all listen up, if those sons of bitches say anything to you,
都不要理他们  听到了吗
you don't react, you hear me?
保持冷静  明白吗
Cool heads. Understood?
这个混蛋会考验你们的
This bastard will try and test you.
好久不见  约翰
Long time, John.
对我来说还不够久  你个狗娘养的
Not long enough for me, you son of a bitch.
不是说要保持冷静吗
What happened to cool heads?
不包括我
I didn't mean me.
你今天又想搞什么鬼
What scam are you running today?
哪有
No scam.
我们在帮度假村放野牛呢
We're babysitting them bison for the resort.
度假村现在还做野牛生意了
Resort's in the buffalo business now?
他们从事旅游业
They're in the tourist business.
收六百块让人骑在上面
Charge 600 dollars for people to ride up here on a dude string
然后给他们拍照
and have pictures taken of 'em.
它们进行布鲁氏菌病检测了吗
These been tested for Brucellosis?
这次人不少啊
Got a whole army now, I see.
他每次带的人都不少  对吧  约翰
He's always got an army. Don't you, John?
检测没问题
Papers are good.
你那天为什么不给他看
Why didn't you show him that the other day?
因为我不喜欢他找我要的态度
'Cause I didn't like the way he asked.
别让我在我们的牧场看到它们
I don't want to see them things on our side of the fence.
法律说阻止它们进入不是我们的工作
Law says it's not our job to keep 'em from getting in.
防止它们乱跑是你们的职责
It's your job to keep 'em from getting out.
你应该很清楚  委员
You should know that, Commissioner.
我不会让它们进来的
Oh, I'll keep 'em out.
但你肯定不会喜欢我的方法
But you're gonna fucking hate the way I do it.
韦德  咱们的宿怨可有点年头了
We're a little long in the tooth for old feuds, Wade.
咱俩除了宿怨  啥都没有
Without old feuds I got none at all.
那还有什么乐趣呢
And where's the fun in that?
去参加葬礼吗
Going to a funeral?
海伦娜那边还有工作
Helena. Got work to do.
我们星期六没有工作
Won't work Saturdays for us,
但你肯定是为自己工作呗
but you're sure working for yourself.
我受够了
Enough of this shit.
我惹他生气了
I've made him mad,
他受不了了
and he's not going to take it anymore.
直奔主题吧
Let's just skip straight to the problem.
我们之间真正的问题
The real problem... between us.
大早上的
It's too early in the morning
翻旧账不好吧  杰米
to dig up that skeleton, Jamie.
反正我就翻了
Well, I'm digging it up anyway.
你知道你危险在哪里吗
You know what is so fucking dangerous about you
那就是你真的相信你在帮忙
is you actually believe that you're helping.
你心里真的相信
Like, in your heart, you believe that.
但是你却拒绝面对你帮助的结果
But you refuse to look at the results of your help.
你拒绝承认你的"帮助"留下的惨痛
You refuse to acknowledge the carnage that your "Help" Leaves behind.
因为作为一个男人  你已经废了
Because as a man you are broken.
你的灵魂和心灵都破碎了
Your soul, your mind is broken.
这可能不是你的错
And, it's not your fault, I guess.
他把你变成了一个你不想成为的人
He made you into something you had no business being.
这可能就是他这么做的原因
I guess that's why he did it.
但你没有对错之分
But there's just no right or wrong with you.
你只想得到他的赞同
Just his approval. That's all that matters to you.
你就是这样的人
That's all you are.
但他不赞同  以及你对此的恐惧
But his disapproval, man, and how much you fear it?
这才是你真正邪恶的原因  杰米
That is what makes you truly evil, Jamie.
你是恶人
And you are evil.
你知道的  你必须知道
You know that. You have to know that.
我所做的一切
All... All I have ever tried to do
都是在保护这个家
is protect this family.
大多数时间都是窝里斗
Most of the time, from itself.
你比任何人都应该清楚
You more than anyone should understand that.
我告诉你一个小秘密
I'm going to tell you a little secret:
你越是变成他想要的样子
the more you become what he wanted you to become,
他就越讨厌你
the more he'll hate you for it.
他是真的讨厌你
And he does hate you for it.
我们都讨厌你
We all do.
我应该拒绝的
I should've said no.
我就不该帮你
That's what I should've done.
因为这样你怀不上孩子
because then you couldn't blame me for doing exactly
就怪不到我头上了
what you asked me to do.
我没让你帮我切除子宫
I didn't ask you for a fucking hysterectomy.
当一个人给其他人带来痛苦时
You know, when you consider the pain that you cause a person
这个人的错
the person's fault...
太邪恶了  杰米
that's evil, Jamie.
你说这很简单的
You said this would be simple.
按理说是很简单
It should have been.
"按理说"就是废话
"Should" Is a useless word.
和"希望"差不多
Almost as useless as "Hope."
他没有改第二个桶的引导  是吗
He didn't change leads around that second barrel, did he?
你够快的话  管他怎么引导的呢
If you're running fast enough it don't matter what lead you're on.
这俩绕桶赛手都挺厉害的
These barrel racers is hands, I'll say that.
宝贝  你能给我扔瓶水吗
Could you toss me a water, babe?
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, sugar.
靠
Damn.
两支舞
Two dances.
我就把她们拉到马场
Here, I'm hauling them to the arena,
帮她们备马  坐在看台上看她们表演了
saddling their horses, sitting in the bleachers watching 'em.
现在我成了牛仔浪妹
Now I'm the damn buckle bunny.
你们没有
You guys didn't, uh...
当然没有  她还不到25岁
'Course not. She ain't even 25 years old.
绕桶赛手就跟痔疮一样  离我越远越好
I need a barrel racer in my life like I need another hemorrhoid.
但我还是在这里帮她拿东西
But here I am anyway, toting her shit around.
你的女人养不起啊
That's a lot of woman you got there.
你住在工棚里  怎么能满足她呢
She's gonna want more than you can offer living in a bunkhouse.
我本来想靠骑烈马离开工棚的
Rodeo was supposed to be my way out of the bunkhouse.
骑烈马和当牛仔一样  不适合谈恋爱
Rodeo's as bad on relationships as cowboying.
没办法分心的  吉米
Can't be married to two things at the same time, Jimmy.
所以你在摔成这个鬼样子
That's what got you banged up in the first place
因为你当时在想她
was thinking about her
没有好好骑那匹烈马
instead of that rocket you was getting on.
反正达顿先生也不让我骑了
Mr. Dutton says I can't do it anymore anyway.
他也跟我说过一次
He told me that too, once.
就在他帮我付了一堆医院账单之后
Right after he paid a stack of my hospital bills.
但唯一能决定要不要继续骑烈马的人是你自己
But the only one that can decide if you rodeo is you.
要不我再参加一次
Maybe I can just do another event.
组队套索
Team rope, maybe.
你拿根十英尺长的绳子都套不到柱子
You can't rope a post with a ten foot loop.
但我从来没见过骑烈马像你骑得这么好的
But you can sit a bucking horse like nothin' I ever seen.
反正我退出以后是没见过了
Least well since I quit, anyway.
我不知道我该怎么办
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
别想太多
You gotta leave your brain out of it,
用心去决定
decide with your heart.
只有这样才不会后悔
It's the only way you'll ever have peace with it.
你什么时候决定退出的
When did you decide to quit?
我的身体替我做了决定
My body decided for me.
现在我每天早上能起床就不错了
Now, it's all I can do to get out of bed every morning.
我想念那种感觉
I miss it.
嗯  我也很想念
Yeah. I miss it too.
谢谢
Thank you.
达顿委员
Commissioner Dutton.
真是太有意思了
It's funny how I can say the same thing
这个称呼几周就换了三个人
and it mean three different people in just as many weeks.
世事无常嘛
Yeah, well, the more things change, you know.
希望不要换汤不换药
I certainly hope they don't stay the same.
我也是
Me, too.
有什么事吗
What can I do for you?
我们这里有个人失踪了
We've got a missing person.
我们这里经常有人失踪
We always have a missing person,
但我们人手老是不够
but we never have the resources to find them.
我已经忍不了了
I'm getting pretty tired of that staying the same.
我不知道我能帮多少忙
Well, I'm not sure how much help I can be
但我尽量  你是这个意思吧
but you've got it, if that's what you're asking for.
有三个探员在那附近
I got three agents close by.
三小时后到
Be there in three hours.
三个也行吧
Three more is something.
你只需要探员
Are you just looking for badges
还是志愿者也行
or do you need volunteers, too?
我们也在招募志愿者团体
We're putting together volunteer groups as well.
我打个电话  看看能不能在帮你找点人
I'll make a call. See if I can't get you some more.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你来见我们
Appreciate you meeting us.
客气
My pleasure.
这是市场股票的首席执行官
This is Market Equities' CEO.
-我是威拉·海斯  -杰米·达顿
- I'm Willa Hayes. - Jamie Dutton.
我们从哪里开始呢
Where should we start?
这是个好问题  杰米
That's a really good question, Jamie.
我没有答案  我真的不知道
I don't have the answer. I really don't know.
我们可以先聊聊你妹的公司卖空我们的股票
We could start with your sister's firm shorting our stock
现在已经成为华尔街的闹剧了
to the point it has become a Wall Street play.
-什么  -我们可以先聊聊那个
- Doing what? - We could start there.
我们也可以聊聊你现在的任职
We could start with being appointed to an office
正好可以没收你家人的财产
that very well could be tasked with condemning your family's property,
但这是一个严重的利益冲突
but that's an obscene conflict of interest.
现在谈论没收有点为时过早吧
I think it's a bit premature to talk condemnation.
你们还没有对土地进行报价呢
You haven't made an offer on the land.
州政府正在购买土地
The State is buying the land.
州政府还没有批准
The State hasn't approved that.
州政府批准这样的收购
And to approve such a purchase the State
需要一个债券倡议
would require a bond initiative
在秋季投票之前
proposed and voted on by the assembly
得到州议会提议并表决通过
before being placed on the fall ballot.
但是你在这里一边要求
And yet, here you are, demanding that
州政府违反了自己的程序
the State violate its own procedures
一边指控州长违反程序
while you accusing the Governor of violating procedure.
成千上万的工作机会
Thousands of jobs.
成千上万的低薪服务工作
Thousands of low paying service jobs.
其他州的技术工人肯定会过来
Skilled labor, I'm sure, will come from out of state.
这会让房价进一步提高
Which will drive the home prices even higher,
前提是你们得逞了
if that's possible.
你在抬高价格  把山谷的人逼走
You're pricing people out of the valley.
他们已经被逼出了山谷  不关我的事
They're already priced out of the valley. That's not my doing.
这叫经济演化
It's called economic evolution.
我不同意
I disagree.
你不是不同意
You don't disagree.
你只是不希望这是真的
You just don't want it to be true.
我有个建议
I have a proposal.
洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
不劳烦州政府买地了
Rather than the State buying the land,
我给你一个报价
I'm gonna make you an offer.
一亩一万  买你的五万亩地
Your fifty thousand acres for ten thousand dollars an acre.
这可是五亿
That's five hundred million dollars.
你们永远也不会为钱发愁了
You'll never be priced out of anything... ever again.
现在不要回答我  好好琢磨一下这个数字
Don't answer me now. Let that number sink in.
我们和州长见面时再讨论这个问题
We'll discuss this again at our meeting with the Governor.
看到那个表情了吗
You see that look?
欲望  对吧  搞定他肯定没问题
Desire. Right? We'll close him.
他并不是最难搞定的人
I don't think he's the hard one to close.
把武器留在卡车里
I'd leave them weapons in the truck.
我们今天不执法
We ain't enforcing no laws today.
好主意
That's good thinking.
如果你们愿意的话  我可以再弄几匹
I can get a few more up here if you want.
谢谢
It's appreciated.
我尽力了
This is all I could wrangle.
我也想再找点人
Wish there were more.
谢谢大家的帮助
It all helps.
伙计们  听着
All right, folks, listen up.
每个人相距十英尺
Everybody stays ten feet apart.
搜寻周围的区域
You scan the area around you.
不要只找塞拉  好吗
No don't just look for Sila, right?
还要找衣服  脚印
You look for clothes, footprints,
一部手机  一串钥匙
a phone, a set of keys.
如果你发现什么  不要碰它
If you find something, do not touch it.
你站在上面  然后大喊
You stand over it, and you shout "hey,"
挥舞你的手臂
and you wave your arm.
警官会过来的
An officer will come to you.
好了  行动吧
All right, let's go.
你认识她吗
Do you know her?
我认识她
I know her.
好孩子
Good kid.
但这种事只会发生在好孩子身上
But this only happens to good kids.
那是狼吗
Is that a wolf?
郊狼
Coyote.
告诉他们别靠近了
Tell them not to come any closer.
大家停下
Everybody stop.
怎么了  他们找到什么了吗
What's happening, did they find something?
是的
They found something.
现场交给你了  本
The scene is yours, Ben.
我们去通知她妈妈
Let's go tell her mother.
布置现场
Set up a crime perimeter.
《骑野牛的人》
}第三集  结局第一部分
这是我这辈子见过的最蠢的事
This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my life.
太精彩了
Oh, it's so good.
你只是不喜欢高质量的电影制作而已
You just don't appreciate quality film making.
我觉得他看起来像
I mean, I feel like he just looks like
有点性感的耶稣骑在野牛上
some kind of like sexy Jesus on the buffalo riding to the--
没人知道你在说什么
No one knows what you're saying.
没人能听懂
No one can understand you.
你能听懂  对吧
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
他怎么不会摔下来啊
How is he staying on that fucking thing?
-它不会弓背啊  -真的吗
- Well, it can't buck. - Really?
不会弓背  不会抬臀
Can't buck, can't rear up.
但它们可以把人滚下来
But they can roll over on your ass.
有人能解释一下他俩的动态吗
I need this whole dynamic explained to me.
一定是因为地球的抖动  造成了一个磁移
It must be the wobble of the earth, creating a magnetic shift--
这就是他被枪击的地方
This is where he gets shot.
小心啊  小心
Look out. Look out!
我们可以在草场骑野牛啊
Hey, we oughta ride the buffalo out there on that field.
等等  什么草场
Wait, what field?
畜栏后面
Out back there behind the corral.
你们的畜栏在哪里
Where are your corrals?
他们能听懂她说话
She speaks, they understand her.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible?
我不是说了么  因为地球的抖动
It's the wobble of the earth, I'm trying to tell you.
畜栏旁边的草场哪有野牛
There ain't no buffalo out in the field by the corrals.
有三十只左右
There's about thirty.
度假村把它们放在那里供游客观赏
The resort put them there for tourists to look at.
还找了一个卑鄙的老混蛋看着它们
And they got this mean old bastard watching them.
-他叫什么名字来着  -韦德什么的
- What was his name? - Wade something.
-韦德  -莫罗
- Wade... - Morrow.
是的  那是他的野牛
Yeah, they're his buffalo.
谁想骑野牛
Who feels like riding a buffalo?
我不想
Not me.
我想骑  但是
Yeah, I would, but, uh...
我不能酒后骑野牛
I'm not supposed to drink and ride buffalos.
你懂的
It's a whole thing.
去他妈的  我要骑野牛
Fuck it, I'll ride a buffalo.
没错  我们要骑  你们这群老娘们可以看着
Yeah, we'll ride the buffalo. You ladies can watch.
有意思
This is gonna be fun.
-等等  真的要骑吗  -可不呗
- Wait. This is happening? - Looks like it.
我这辈子干过一些蠢事
I've done some dumb shit in my life.
但肯定没这个蠢
This is gonna be dumber.
有什么好办法吗
Well, what's the best way to do this?
不能用绳子套住它们的脖子
Well, you can't rope them around the neck.
这样会破坏它们的喉头
You'll crush their larynx.
所以只能套住它们的角
So you gotta rope them by their horns.
然后呢
And then what?
然后把它们拉住
And then you pull them to a stop.
跳上去就行了
You jump on and off you go--
我只是来看看的
I'm just here to watch.
我来
I'll do it.
这必须得喝一点
We can't be sober for this.
操  它们多可爱啊
Shit, what a baby bunch.
绕桶赛女孩会害死我们的
Barrel racer girls are gonna get us killed.
而且她们都不是我们的人
And they ain't even our girls.
好样的
Atta girl!
你没事吧
You all right?
太爽了
That was fuckin' awesome.
下一个是谁
Who's next?
到我了
Fuck me, baby.
再套一头吧
Let's go rope another one.
感觉好点了吗
Feeling any better?
这是不对的
It's just not right.
的确
No, it's not.
世界上到处都是怪物
There's monsters everywhere in this world.
找到以后就立即处决
You just gotta kill them when you find them.
但你找不到它们
But you can't find them.
他们甚至没有足够的警察来寻找受害者
Hell, they don't even have enough police to look for the victims.
我还好意思坐在浴缸里
And here I am, sitting in this swimming pool of a bathtub.
你不要自责  宝贝
You can't make it your fault, baby.
我不是在自责  我只是在思考解决办法
I'm not making it my fault. I'm making it my problem.
莫妮卡  你知道我们无法阻止这个腐朽的世界
You know we can't stop the world from being bad, Monica.
这并不意味着我们不能尝试
Doesn't mean we shouldn't try.
早上好  爸爸
Good morning, daddy.
今早是挺好的
Yes, it is.
你在练瑜伽吗
Have you been practicing yoga?
练习什么
Practicing what?
我只是在捉摸你为什么心平气和的
I'm just trying to understand this new inner peace you've found.
这个地方面对的
What this place is facing...
不是敌人
it isn't an enemy.
而是一种观点
It's a perspective.
价值观的转变
It's a shift in values.
世界不再重视你的生活方式了  爸爸
The world doesn't value your way of life anymore, Dad.
我知道
I know.
你不能把这场战斗交给杰米
You can't delegate this fight to fuckin' Jamie.
好吧  还有
Okay, and...
凯斯  他没有耐心和技巧
Kayce, he just doesn't have the patience or the skill.
还有
And...
我一个人做不到
I can't do it by myself.
但你必须做到  亲爱的
But you have to, honey.
你得教导凯斯
You have to teach Kayce.
以及学会如何信任杰米
And you have to learn how to trust Jamie.
相信杰米
Trust Jamie?
等等  是你
Wait, you're the...
是你告诉我不能相信杰米的
you're the one telling I shouldn't trust Jamie.
贝丝  就算我再保这里十年
What does it matter, Beth, if I keep this place
然后因为你想不明白  你们三个丢弃了这片土地
for another ten years and the three of you lose it
那还有什么意义呢
because you couldn't figure it out?
-不  -贝丝
- No. - Beth...
你不了解他
You don't know him!
贝丝  你知道什么我们其他人不知道的吗
And what is it you know, Beth, that the rest of us don't?
他做了什么  贝丝
What did he do, Beth?
他做了什么
What did he do?
贝丝  如果你不告诉我  我可帮不了你
I can't help you, Beth if you won't tell me what it is.
停车  老莫
Pull over, Mo.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
寻找线索
Looking for clues.
想帮帮忙
Trying to help.
你在这里唯一能发现的就是
The only thing you're going to find out here
她之前所发现的
is exactly what she found.
这帮不上什么忙
That's not gonna help anything.
这不公平
It's not fair.
嗯  当然
No. It certainly isn't.
但是从一开始就是这样设计的
But it was designed that way. From the beginning.
我们不应该在这里
We're not supposed to be here.
保留地本来只是个暂时的落脚点
Reservations were supposed to be temporary.
我们应该学习白人
We were supposed to learn how to be white
去城市生活
and then go live in cities
然后这块地也会被卖掉
and then this land would be sold, too.
但我们没有学习白人
But we didn't learn to be white.
我们不想学
Wouldn't.
现在弄成了这样
And now here we are.
政府不会帮忙  因为他们不想帮忙
The government won't help because it doesn't want to.
政府想让我们死
It wants us to die.
政府想让我们离开
It wants us gone.
因为政府想要土地
Because it wants the land.
这是政府一直以来的诉求
And that's all it's ever wanted.
所以我想要回我们的土地
That's why I want our land back.
所有的土地
All of it.
这样我们就可以构建他们无法夺走的生命
So we can build lives that they can't take away.
我能帮上什么忙
How do I help?
我要组建一个理事会
I'm forming a council
重点针对保留地妇女遭遇暴力问题
to focus on violence against women on the reservation.
我要把我们的故事传递到大学
It will take our stories to the universities.
到国会  传递给愿意倾听的人们
To Congress. To anyone who will listen.
我们的第一场战斗是反对被忽视的现状
Our first fight is against being ignored.
你愿意领导这场战斗吗
Would you like to lead that fight?
我可以
I could lead that fight.
那你就算帮上忙了
That's how you help.
太好了
Oh, good.
我想和你谈谈
I need to talk to you about something.
市场股票集团提出
The Market Equities Group made an--
我这辈子做过这么多承诺  儿子
Of all the promises I've made in my life, son.
要不是我那么爱你母亲
If I didn't love your mother so much...
我肯定会食言
I would break it.
我发誓我肯定会食言
I swear to God I would break it.
出什么事了吗  什么情况
Did something happen? I don't understand.
三十年后怎么办  杰米
What happens in thirty years, Jamie?
等你和你的兄弟姐妹老了
When you, and your brother and sister
无法为这里而战
are too old to fight for this place
泰特就只能孤身作战了吗
and Tate has to fight for it on his own?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
李不会结婚  他不想要孩子
Lee wouldn't marry, didn't want children.
我怀疑你也一样
I doubt you will either.
现在你妹因为你怀不上孩子了
And now your sister can't. She can't because of you.
-爸  等等  -别动
- Dad, wait, wait. - Quit moving!
我没有
I didn't.
我  操
I-- Fuck.
是她来找我的
She came to me.
她很害怕
She was scared.
我也很害怕
I was scared.
你为什么要让她绝育  杰米
Why would you take that from her, Jamie?
你凭什么让她绝育
Who the fuck did you think you were to take that from her?
怎么了
What the hell is going on here?
问你哥
Ask your brother.
我所做的一切都是在付出
All I do is give!
我恨他  我恨死他了
I hate him. I fucking hate him.
我恨你
I fucking hate you!
这一切都是徒劳的
It's all for nothing.
我所做的一切
Everything I've done. It's...
都是徒劳无功
It's all for nothing.